newroads.org 2014-12-16

# New Roads School Omni Footer - Privacy Policy

New Roads School values and respects your privacy. This policy governs its Web site data collection via www.newroads.org and lt.newroads.org. By using the New Roads School Web site, you are deemed to have consented to the practices described in this policy.

**Collection of Personal Information**

New Roads School shall keep confidential personal information that it collects such as first and last name, electronic mail address, home or other physical address, telephone number, and fax number.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by New Roads School. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by New Roads School for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the New Roads School Web site.

**Use of Personal Information**

New Roads School will inform you of the purpose for its collection of information. It does not intend to transfer or otherwise share your personal information to third parties without your consent, except under the limited conditions described below. If you choose to provide us with your personal information, the information will be stored on a secure server and we will use that information at New Roads School or we may transfer it third party service provider as necessary. New Roads School will not record your credit card number.

New Roads School may also collect electronic information during your use of its Web site. New Roads School may collect domain information to enable it to analyze how visitors use this site. This data enables New Roads School to become more familiar with people who visit its site including how often they visit, their access times, and browser type. New Roads School will use this information to improve its services and obtain statistics regarding the use of its site.

New Roads School may also use the information to which it has access to provide you with or solicit other information and to let you know of additional services that may be of interest to you.

**Use of Cookies**

Some pages on this site may use “cookies”—small files that the site places on your hard drive for identification purposes. Cookies cannot read information from your hard drive. They will also not run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.

A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID to track the pages visited, but the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply. These files are used for site registration and to customize your visit to the site. The cookie will tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page on the Web site, and it will customize the site’s features for you.

Your Web browser may notify you when you are receiving a cookie and it may give you the choice to accept or reject it. You can set your browser to warn you about cookies, and to determine if you want to refuse all cookies. If you chose not to accept cookies, some pages may not fully function and you may not be able to access certain information on this site.

**Information Sharing**

New Roads School does not share your information without your permission, except if you consent to share your information to a third party service provider working on New Roads School’s behalf.

New Roads School will also disclose your personal information, if required to do so by law, or in urgent circumstances, such as, but not limited to, those that involve the need to protect an individual’s personal safety, the protection of the public or the protection of New Roads School’s rights or property. New Roads School will not trade, sell, rent, lease, or otherwise share your information to anyone, or let anyone use it except if you have authorized its use.

**Protecting the Privacy of Children**

Children under 13 years old are not the target audience for our Web site. To protect their privacy, New Roads School prohibits the solicitation of personal information from these children.

**Internet Security**

New Roads School strives to protect your personal information; however, we urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Please take proactive steps to secure your personal data, such as frequently changing your passwords.

**Links to Third Party Sites**

New Roads School’s Web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. New Roads School encourages you to learn about the privacy practices and policies of those companies.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

New Roads School reserves the right to change, modify or update this policy at any time without notice. Any substantial changes in the way New Roads School uses your personal information will be posted on this site.

**Contact Information**

New Roads School welcomes your comments regarding its privacy policy. If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at (310) 828-5582 or via email at [eyen@newroads.org](mailto:eyen@newroads.org).
